She has been arrested. She's here on our campus here.
She's being there. My detectives are finishing up with some interviews with her at this time.
And then once they have concluded, she will be escorted into the county jail.
You know, the whole time we had only one side of the story, OK?
We know that she shot through the door.
Of course, on her side of the story, she makes claims that her life was being threatened.
And the way the laws are written in this state, and this is what people need to understand,
and our hands are tied in law enforcement in these cases where we are instructed that we cannot make the arrest
because we have to rule out whether the shooting was justified or unjustified.
So one of the biggest things is the interview of witnesses, and some of our witnesses were the mother's kids.
And obviously, we were not going to interview them that night after watching their mother be shot and killed.
Don't let anyone tell you that this happened because they did the right thing.
This happened because folks raised their voices, because folks organized,
because folks got focused around not allowing this police department to simply brush Adjika's life under the rug.
As Black people in this country, particularly in racist Florida,
we cannot count on policing to be done in a fair and practical manner.
Ocala is a town riddled with racism.
Let's keep going, let's keep being loud, and let's keep being present.
Good job, y'all.